alreadyhosting.com 2016-04-13

# Privacy Policy | Top 10 WebHosting Companies|Upto 80% off Special Promo Links

Internet Strategies, LLC (“We”, “Company”, “Our”, or “Us”) is the owner of AlreadyHost.com (“Website”). It is our responsibility to protect the privacy of the users on our site (“You” or “Your”) through our compliance with the items contained in this Privacy Policy (“Policy”). The Policy, tells you about the kind of information we collect how we use, protect and sometimes disclose such information while you are using the site.

It is your responsibility to read the Policy carefully. If you disagree with any of the statements contained within the policy, you agree to immediately quit using the website in any form and manner whatsoever.

Amendments

At any time we reserve the right to change this Policy with our discretion and without prior notice to individuals. Changes will be effective once posted on this Website page. If you continue to use the Website you are implying the acceptance of the amended Policy. We requested to visit the Policy regularly to remain updated on the amended Policy.

Applicability

This Policy is applicable for any information collected through the Website, any email, text or electronic communication with you, or through mobile-based application that enables use of the service, which is otherwise provided online through the Website.

Information Collection

**Non-personally Identifiable Information:**  We also reserve the right to collect certain non-personally identifiable information from your use of the Website. These items do not directly identify you. This information may include, without limitation,

  * the operating system installed on your computer system,
  * the browser you used to access the Website,
  * your Internet Protocol (IP) Address,
  * the IP Address of your Internet Service Provider (ISP),
  * location data,
  * traffic data,
  * communication data,
  * browsing patterns (for instance, Website pages most visited, time spent on each page, action taken on each page, etc.)

**Personally Identifiable Information:**  During your use of the Website, we may collect certain personally identifiable information including, without limitation,

  * your name,
  * age,
  * gender,
  * postal address,
  * email address,
  * telephone number,
  * company name,
  * company website URL
  * job title and
  * other company details.

This information will only be collected when you voluntarily provide us with the requested details during your use of the Website. This includes and is not limited to; information submitted while filling forms on the Website, reporting a problem in the Website, responding to surveys and questionnaires.

Technological tools like the following below, are used to collect the non-personally identifiable information:

(a)  Cookies, which are small text files that are deposited on the hard drive of your computer system by default when you visit the Website to access Website service. You may refuse to accept cookies by adjusting your browser preferences. However, we strongly advise against refusing the cookies from our servers for two reasons: (i) our cookies neither compromise on your online privacy, nor do they harm your computer system in any manner whatsoever; and (b) by refusing cookies, you may not be able to access some portions of our Website service.

(b)  Web Beacons, which are, essentially, clear GIF files that offer multiple benefits, like counting users who have visited Website pages or opened an e-mail and for recording the popularity of certain Website content and verifying system and server integrity.

Privacy of Children

The intended Website is for use by persons who are eligible to enter into a valid contract. We recommend the website is not used by children under 13 years old. If you are under the age of 13 years, we request that you stop any further use of the Website. If you suspect that we are in possession of any information or data related to children below 13 years, please contact us at alreadyhosted@gmail.com for immediate remedial action.

It is highly suggested that children older then 13, but younger then 18 years old use the Website with parental/guardian consent. If you are within the age range previously stated, you imply and warrant that you have parental/guardian consent to use the Website.

Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information

The non-personally identifiable information is used to:

(a)  prevent repeated login during an active session, on the Website or switching to different features of the Website

(b)   improve our Website, it’s content and services in order to deliver a more customized solution.

(c)   research browsing patterns for internal use,

(d)  customize our site Website to your uses

(e)  give you the services you need.

Your non-personally identifiable information might be shared with our affiliates under confidentiality conditions. We prohibit the use of this information for any purpose other then listed above.

Use of Personally Identifiable Information

We reserve the right to use the personally identifiable information collected for the following purposes:

(a)  to customize the services on the Website

(b)  to give you the information you request from us,

(c)  to fulfill your requests on the Website,

(d)  to communicate to you about information on the Website

(e)  to give notices,

(f)    to identify any changes on the Website

(g)  for any other purpose for which the use of personally identifiable information is indispensable.

Our mailing list is used to help communicate these items to you, however you may choose to not receive emails by clicking unsubscribe. We do however reserve the right to send important information, even if you have opted out of our mailing list.

We will only use your information for the purposes stated above. We do not sell, rent or lease out or in any way, commercially exploit any of your information.

Access to Information

Updates to your account can be made by logging into your account and managing your profile settings. Emails can also be sent to alreadyhosted@gmail.com, with the specific request to update your personally identifiable information in our records. We may however, not be able to update all the requested information in case it violates any applicable law. Sometimes information may be un-editable without creating a new account.

Disclosure of Information

Information is not disclosed without your consent. However, under the following circumstances, we may disclose your information without incurring any liability or without your consent:

(a)  disclosure in compliance with an order from an appropriate legal entity, including court, or for the purposes of obeyance of legal processes,

(b)  disclosure to enforce our legal rights and other rights as provided for in our Terms of Use Agreement,

(c)  disclosure to prevent fraud or any other alleged illegality on the Website,

(d)  disclosure to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our customers or others,

(e)  disclosure to the successor-in-interest in case of sale, or substantial sale, of assets of the Company.

Data Security

Our website has been issued strong human and technological safeguards to prevent loss or misuse of your information with your use of the Website. However, despite some of the best technology safeguards, there is no mechanism that guarantees to prevent loss or unauthorized access to sensitive information stored on our servers by hackers due to rapid advancement in technology. For all such accidental or inadvertent data loss, the Internet Strategies, LLC shall not be liable to anyone.

You are completely responsible for any authorized or unauthorized use of your account, regardless of whether the activity in your account is legitimate. It is your responsibility for the safety and integrity of your username and password.

Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns with the Website, please contact us at alreadyhosted@gmail.com. We shall strive to answer all your question within 24 hours or our earliest convenience.
